party411.com 2014-04-29

# Privacy Policy

We want you to know that we respect your privacy and value you as a customer. To this end, we have initiated policies to ensure that your personal information is handled safely and responsibly.  
Please note:

Whether or not you have viewed this Privacy Policy, or the terms and conditions of use of this Web site, and whether or not you have chosen to not receive notices from us, this Privacy Policy and those terms and conditions will still govern your use of the Party411.com Web site. We may update or change our Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time, as we determine is appropriate. It is your responsibility to review them for changes.

 **411Unlimited, LLC** , has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and information sharing practices for this Web site: [http://www.party411.com](http://www.party411.com/).

Customer Information  
We may request that you provide us with personal information, and we receive and gather information (such as customer name, mailing address, billing and/or shipping addresses, phone number, e-mail address, and, when necessary, credit card information) from you, which we may use for the following purposes:

  * To process orders
  * To limit the likelihood of fraud or error when we process your orders or any requests for refunds or exchanges 
  * To improve customer shopping experiences and improve the effectiveness of our Web site and marketing activities 
  * To provide party planning information
  * To allow customers to participate in events or other activities we offer or promote
  * To send marketing and other communications about our products and services 
  * To fulfill catalog or other requests 
  * To send order and shipping confirmation e-mails 
  * To receive information from customers or contact customers about their order or other interaction with our Web site
  * To conduct contests, promotions or surveys 
  * Internal record keeping

We also may collect demographic information from you, including age, personal interests and product preferences.

If you have created an account you may see the information we hold about you by logging in and reviewing your account. You are able to correct the information when logged in.

If you do not create an account with us you may request details of personal information which we hold about you. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to the address below:

411Unlimited, LLC d/b/a Party411.com   
4949 Galaxy Parkway, Suite G  
Cleveland, Ohio, 44128  
USA  
Attention: Chief Privacy Officer 

or 

email us at [mail@party411.com](mailto:mail@party411.com)

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

Sharing of Personal Information; Third Party Services

Personal information that you provide to us may be shared by us with our affiliates and strategic partners so that they may offer you products and services, and with employees, agents and third party contractors who assist us in operating, maintaining and administering our Web site. The third parties with whom we conduct business are authorized to use your information only to perform the service for which they are hired. They are required to abide by the terms of our Privacy Policy including taking reasonable measures to ensure your personal information is secure. 

We also may transfer or sell all or a substantial part of the information we have collected from customers, including personal information, to any person or entity that may merge with or acquire our company, or that otherwise may acquire a significant part of our assets or business, or in connection with a dissolution or similar event. 

We use third-party service providers to send regular mail or email marketing communications to you, to process credit card payments, to provide product recommendations, and to provide other services that may enhance your shopping experience on our Web site. These companies may use information about your visits to this Web site in order to provide personalized recommendations and advertisements about our goods and services on our Web site as well as when you visit other Web sites. 

This site contains links to other Web sites. Party411.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

When we share your information with other companies to help us provide our services to you, we will require them to comply with all applicable legal requirements regarding the privacy of your information. Except as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, we will NOT sell or rent your e-mail address or password with a third party. We understand that this information is private, and we will handle it in a responsible manner. 

From time to time, we may be required to share personal information by reason of a valid court order or subpoena, or in connection with a government investigation or as otherwise required by law. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe may be unlawful. We may share certain personal information that you have provided to us when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of others and our company.

E-mails/Newsletters  
You may sign up to receive promotional e-mails and newsletters on our Web site to find out about current specials, offers, sales, and more. If at any time you wish to stop receiving these e-mails, you have the option to remove your name from our mailing list. At the bottom of each e-mail/newsletter, you can click on a link to unsubscribe and remove your name.

Public Forums  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. We have no responsibility if you do post personal information. Subject to the other provisions of this Privacy Policy relating to your personal information, you grant a perpetual worldwide non-exclusive license to Party411.com to copy, use and/or display any content that you post on our Web site.

Collection of Children's Personal Information  
We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information online from children under the age of 13. 

Choice/Opt-Out  
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications. 

  1. You can send email to [mail@party411.com ](mailto:mail@party411.com)
  2. You can call the following telephone number: 216-514-8411 

Before sending you mobile marketing (e.g., text messages on your cell phone) we will require your express consent by requesting that you opt-in. If you no longer wish to receive these mobile marketing text messages, you may opt-out by following the instructions provided in the text messages you receive. 

Please allow a reasonable time for us to respond to your request to opt out of any of our marketing communications. Typically, we attempt to process any request to opt out in accordance with the following guidelines: 

> 7 business days for e-mails   
>  30 business days for direct mail and phone   
> 

Until your requested change takes effect, you may still receive marketing communications from us. If your opt out request is sent by regular mail, please allow extra time for us to receive and process your notice. 

Even if you notify us that you would like to opt out of receiving marketing communications, you may still receive business-related communications from us such as order confirmations, product recall notices, and other communications based on other contact or interaction that you may have had with our Web site or with our affiliates and strategic partners.

Correct/Update Information  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. You can send email to [mail@party411.com ](mailto:mail@party411.com)
  2. You can call the following telephone number: 216-514-8411 

Third Party Advertising and Cookies  
In some cases, Party411 works with third parties who serve ads to this site. These ads may contain cookies. These third parties may use anonymous information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites. We may also share anonymous information with these companies in aggregate form. In either case, the purpose of the sharing is to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you, analyzing and improving the effectiveness of ads and e-mails, and improving and enhancing our site and its content. 

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are placed by us on your computer through your web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser when you make future visits to our Web site, and to store certain information between visits.

You can stop your computer from storing cookies if you want to. Most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Because cookies allow you to make full use of the features on our Web site, we recommend that you leave them turned on.

We may also use other means of tracking your activities on our Web site or in any e-mails we send to you for marketing purposes. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. We may use these to compile tracking information reports regarding the demographics of our users, and Web site traffic patterns and purchases. We may then provide these reports to advertisers and others. As a general matter, the tracking information in these reports is not easily connected to the personal information of individual users, and is not used for such purpose. If these tracking graphics are used in our HTML-based emails, they let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. If you do not want to receive these e-mails, please see the “unsubscribe” section below. For research purposes we may link tracking information with personal information voluntarily provided by Web site users. Once such a link is made, all of the linked information will be treated as personal information and will be used and disclosed only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Security  
We take your business seriously and will use reasonable precautions to make your shopping experience safe. We use Secure Socket Layer encrypting to keep your private information and credit card information secure.

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

411Unlimited, LLC  
4949 Galaxy Parkway, Suite G, Cleveland, Ohio, 44128, USA   
216-514-8411
